This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
a legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Munky D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
This is exciting!
I can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cover path across the Grand Line to the New World.
The Straw Hat crew, leading their ship coated before their journey to Fishman Island,
landed on the Sabaody Archipelago in search of a coating mechanic.
Little did they know, the man they were looking for was once the vice-captain of the Roger Pirates.
After finding him, they were ambushed by Sentomaru of the Marine Science Unit.
Where are you from?
Luffy!
To make matters worse, they were also pitted against the Marine Admiral Kizaru,
who proved too deadly a foe for the exhausted Straw Hats.
Well, you'll have plenty of time to rest up now.
ZARU!
Are you sure you want to do this, Dark King Rayleigh?
Don't go picking these buds before they sprout.
Their era is only just beginning, and I want to see what they do with it.
Rayleigh!
Thanks to Rayleigh's help, the crew made a hasty retreat.
But before they could celebrate, they were stopped dead in their tracks by Bartholomew Kumar,
a warlord of the sea.
You and I will never meet again.
Farewell, Straw Hat.
And so the Straw Hat crew disappeared from Zabahodi,
suffering absolute defeat.
Lynn!
The all-female island Amazon Lily!
Damn it.
If I could just wink right, I'd be even more handsome.
Put-a-put-a-put-a-put-a.
Click.
Good news, Duval, we found it!
It's at a bay by group 41.
I got it!
I'll be right there!
All right, men, listen up!
The pride of the Rosie Life Riders is on the line here!
We can't lose!
Yes, sir!
Grove 41!
Now come on, Motobalo!
Go!
Vroom!
I wonder what those shockwaves were about.
They shook the whole archipelago.
I hope the young master and his friends are all right.
What do you mean you haven't caught them?
Admiral Kizaru is pursuing them as we speak, so I'm sure it's only a matter of time until
they're captured, ma'am.
You bunch of useless dogs!
Not only did you allow them to do this to my father and brother, you also let every last
one of our slaves escape.
And yet I must save my contempt for the pirates who made a mockery of our bloodline.
When you catch those heathens, I'll show them a true living hell until they beg for death
on their knees.
Hey Duval, I mean Hanson, what do you think's taking the straw hats so long?
Hmm?
Maybe those guys are still chasing them.
I heard things are a mess at the port right now.
Yeah.
I saw it from the air myself.
Pirates and Marines were fighting like crazy.
Hope they didn't get caught in that.
Stay sharp.
With all of those idiots running wild all over Saba Odi, who knows if their ship will
be safe?
That's why we've got to guard it with our very lives.
Until the coding craftsman shows up and takes over, don't budge and itch!
You got that, Rosie Life Riders?
Roger, Captain Handsome!
Rah!
I have a bad feeling about this all of a sudden.
I sure hope Luffy Chin and his friends are okay out there.
Come on, Kamey, don't say stuff like that.
You're just going to stress everybody out.
Yeah, but...
You, the straw hats are tough, you know that.
There's nothing to worry about.
I hope you're right.
Knock it off, Kamey.
You're scaring me over nothing here.
Straw hat might not be the brightest, but he won't lose in a fight.
You've seen how strong that guy is.
But not stronger than an admiral.
I'm not saying that they'll lose, but this will take more than just strength.
No?
The seas ahead will be rough for them, filled with waves the likes of which have never been
seen before.
And yet they must withstand them, ride them.
It's quiet, but can you hear it?
Little by little, the tides are changing, and the world with them.
After being ejected from Sabahodi, Monkey D. Luffy found himself on a very unique journey.
Zoro, Nami, I'm sorry, Usam, Soji, Chopper!
Robin!
Frankie, Brooke!
Everybody!
Where did you go?
You guys can't be dead!
Dammit, there was nothing I could do!
That stupid warlord is going to pay for this!
I hate this!
It sucks!
How far am I going to fly anyway?
Oh.
Hey, wait a second.
But someone might tell you he can send you flying for three days and nights with those
paw pads.
Can't say if it's true or not, but that's the rumor.
But that could be good news.
Maybe everyone didn't disappear.
They're just flying around like me.
But that axe guy was telling the truth.
Although three days of this sure will be boring.
If I fall in the ocean, that'll be the end of me.
I'm still hungry too.
Screw this.
I'm going to sleep.
Zoro.
Nami.
Usam.
Sanji.
Chopper.
Robin.
Frankie.
Brooke.
All my friends.
On and on he soared through starry skies.
Then, at long last...
I've just...
Fuck.
Look.
I'm alive.
I know what happened, but I don't think my rubber power saved me this time.
Also, what's this bear paw looking thing doing on the ground?
If everyone else had a landing like this, they might be okay.
Oh, well. Gotta get back.
Where am I?
Which way is the Sabo-Odi Archipelago from here?
Wait a sec.
I have my Bebra card, of course.
All right, good thing everyone got one, huh?
Let's go. Easy. Follow the card.
We'll be back together in no time.
That way.
Everyone start running and look after yourselves!
We can't win this one!
We're too weak!
Get moving!
Just go! Get out of there!
We can figure out a plan once we're safe!
Run!
Why the hell am I so weak?
I couldn't save any of them.
What's wrong with me?
Actually, that didn't hurt that bad.
That rock's still in the way.
No doubt about it.
The card's pointing in that direction.
Fine.
Giant pistol!
Man, I can't do it.
I'm all out of power.
I need food.
Sanji!
Who am I kidding?
I know he's not here.
Thanks for all the food, buddy.
That really brings me back.
Grandpa Garp used to throw me in the jungle all the time when I was a kid.
Actually, that kind of sucked.
This place is awfully quiet for a jungle.
Feels lonely.
Hey, aren't these laughing mushrooms?
Perfect!
This is just what I need right now.
Yeah, now I'm having fun!
Even though I'm all alone!
Ooh, these look weird.
Let's try them!
Now I'm mad!
Laughing mushrooms!
Hey, look!
There's more over here!
Oh, crying mushroom!
Hurry!
I can see the smoke!
It's right over there!
They've been anchored offshore for a while.
You don't think they made landfall in secret, do you?
If so, this could be of great consequence.
True, but that scenario is highly unlikely.
We have heavy security all over the island.
Even if they did find a way to breach our iron defenses,
they would be foolish to draw attention to themselves with a campfire.
Then who could it be?
We'll just have to find out for ourselves.
Let's split up into groups.
Got it!
The End
What is that?
Margaret, hurry!
You must see this!
Look!
Calm down.
I'm right here, Sweet Pea.
What do you make of it?
Huh?
Rather puzzling, isn't it?
Hmm.
Oh, this is terrible!
I think this is a human!
Is she from the village?
I don't know.
There are so many mushrooms growing out of her body, I can't even tell.
Then the fire.
Do you think it may have actually been a call for help?
Hmm.
Aha!
Look here!
This must be why she ate these!
A parasitic mushroom.
When you eat one, a whole sea of them pop up all over your body.
We have to do something!
Or these mushrooms will sap away all of her strength and she'll die.
Then make haste before all is lost.
Off Alondra!
Carry her to the village, and quickly!
K!
Stay strong, small one.
We will find aid.
Let's hope.
We have an emergency!
Hey!
Down in front!
I can't see!
Goodness!
Mushrooms!
What happened?
I haven't seen that girl in the village before.
Have you?
No.
Not me.
Hey!
Who is that?
With all those mushrooms, it's hard to tell.
Any idea where she came from?
Is she alive?
She ate a parasitic mushroom and now they're growing all over her body.
Belladonna, what do you think we should do?
You can pull them off, but we have to get them all.
Be thorough.
Huh?
They come off?
Oh, wow.
But some of the bases are still stuck.
Don't worry.
I'll take care of them later.
Just keep pulling.
She's so odd.
Are you sure that this was wise?
What could I do?
She was barely alive when we found her.
I thought she might be from the village.
Phew.
Well, that should do it.
Good.
Now step back a bit.
Huh?
No!
I'm on fire!
Put me out!
Hold on.
Belladonna!
What are you doing?
This is the only way to keep them from growing back.
Still, it seems a bit excessive.
She passed out again.
Well, that's interesting.
It seems she was covered in injuries before she was covered in mushrooms.
She was?
She must have gone through quite the terrible battle.
We need to treat her wounds.
Do me a favor, Margaret.
Take her down to the river and give her a good bath.
Uh, yes.
Yes, of course.
Well, it appears that she's not from the village after all.
How strange.
Yes.
Huh?
Hold on.
What is this?
Is something wrong?
We've been remiss in our mushroom picking duties.
There's one between her legs that we failed to catch.
How careless of us.
Huh.
You're right, but this one seems different than the others, doesn't it?
It has such a strange shape.
Wait, look.
It's another one.
Here, see?
Right on the bottom.
It appears to be some sort of sack mushroom.
Better plot.
It won't come off.
But why?
Hey, what's going on?
What happened?
It's stretching.
What is?
A mushroom.
Let me see.
That sounds funny.
That's enough.
Stop gawking, ladies.
They aren't putting on a show for you.
Huh?
If we leave, so do you.
Hey, look.
That isn't normal, is it?
It's strange.
She's sort of rugged.
Not very well endowed, either.
It's no use.
Come over here, Afalandra.
Afalandra, you give it a try.
Me?
Are you sure?
Mm-hmm.
Give it a yank.
It'll come right off.
Why don't we all pull on it?
That'll work.
No.
Huh?
If the mushroom refuses to come off,
then we must burn it as Belladonna did,
until naught but ashes remain.
Yes, a splendid idea.
Wouldn't you agree, Margaret?
Sure, burn away.
Oh, my.
What's this?
Is something wrong?
Oh, hello, Granny Nyon.
There's a mushroom growing on this girl
that won't come off no matter how hard we try.
Do you think we should all pull it together?
Or just burn it off?
Oh, goodness.
But who is she?
Hmm.
The mushroom's a mystery, too.
Let's see.
Where could it be?
Oh, no!
Whoa.
Hey, Granny Nyon, you aren't ill, are you?
No, everything is just fine.
Except that this person is a...
This person is a...
Hey.
It's a man!
A man!
No!
I've never seen a man before.
Whatever shall I do?
Here lies the maiden island of Amazon Lily,
inhabited by a tribe of female warriors
known as the Kuja.
Woe be to the man who dreams of this land,
and woe be to the man who seeks it.
For if they shall ever set foot upon its soil,
death surely awaits them.
Captured by the women of Amazon Lily,
Luffy tries to escape
and hopes of reuniting with his friends.
However, the snake princess is returning to the island,
and if she learns a man has been brought to the village,
both Luffy and the women who rescued him
could pay the ultimate price.
On the next One Piece,
hurry back to your friends,
the maiden island adventure.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!